Natasha Doowa

Mobile:085-591-9496

Email: Tashadoowa@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Experienced, dedicated and passionate Bachelor Degree and Master Degree professor. Teaching students on-site and online from numerous social and cultural backgrounds, possessing exceptional administrative, verbal communication and written skills along with constructive and effective teaching techniques that promotes a stimulating learning atmosphere. Taught various college subjects under Business and Hospitality discipline, involved in teaching IELTS, Business English, Training programs, public speaking and much more. Would love to share my knowledge and experience with the young innovative minds. Fluent in both Thai and English.



Work History

MBA Lecturer

• Stamford International University, Bangkok Thailand......2017 - 2021

Position: Head of Program and Advisor to Undergraduate degree students Lecturer for Business and Technology Program:

Course taught from 2015- 2021:

Business courses such as Principles of Marketing, Principles of Management, Business Communications, Customer Relationship Management, Strategic Management, Introduction to Research, Market Research Technique and Leading Teams to Success. **Hospitality courses** such as Principle of Event Management, MICE Fundamentals, Introduction

Hospitality courses such as Principle of Event Management, MICE Fundamentals, Introduction to Hospitality, Rooms Inventory and Cost Management

Education and Qualifications

• Raffles International College Bangkok

Bachelor Degree in Commerce Major in (Management), 2013

- Assumption University of Thailand (ABAC)
 - Master of Business Administration, 2015
- Assumption University of Thailand

Ph.D. in Educational Leadership

Doctor of Philosophy in Educational Leadership, 2017-2022

Key Competencies and Skills

- MICE/Event service from planning, coordinating and the execution of event
- Sponsorship Management
- Research skills